&gt；&gt；steve kinney：那么让我们看看我们是否能摆脱它。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So
let's see if we can get rid of it.
我最喜欢的库之一叫做
One of my favorite libraries is called
反应可加载。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：和
React Loadable.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
React Loadable所做的是它利用了两个方面的优势。
what React Loadable does is it kind
of takes advantage of two things.
Webpack开箱即用支持这种新的ES6语法，
Webpack out of the box
supports this new es6 syntax,
这允许您有一个返回承诺的导入。
which allows you to have
an import that returns a promise.
发生的事情是，你说进口，它会继续去取东西，然后
What happens is, you say import and
it will go ahead and fetch the thing, and
那么当我们获得我们想要的访问权限时，承诺就会得到解决。
then the promise will resolve when we
have the access we're looking for.
所以你会说，稍后去拿这个，一旦你有了它就做代码，对吗？
So you'll be like, go get this later and
do the code once you have it, right?
这就像，这件事的一个关键部分。
Which is like, one key piece of this.
react loadable只是让我们对此进行了非常快速的抽象。
React Loadable just gives us a really
quick abstraction over this.
也就是说，你可以拿一个组件，你知道它有很大的依赖性。
Which is you can take a component that you
know has some pretty big dependencies.
你可以说，嘿，当我们使用这个组件的时候，
And you can say like, hey,
go ahead when we use this component,
去加载，比如请求额外的代码块。
go and load, like ask for
that extra chunk of code.
同时，显示此加载组件。
In the meantime,
show this loading component.
那可能是个旋转器。
That could be a spinner.
很多时候你会看到的模式，特别是你会在Facebook上看到它。
A lot of times you'll see the pattern of,
especially you'll see it in Facebook.
如果你在Facebook加载你的时间线之前打开它，你会看到空的，
If you open Facebook up before it's
loaded your timeline, you see empty ones,
好像那是一种骷髅模型。
like that's kind of skeleton model.
您可以向用户显示表明您正在获得其余内容的内容。
You can show the user something that
indicates you're getting the rest.
然后把它放到合适的地方。
And put it in place then.
好的一点是，如果你只取一次，它就不会再这么做了。
The nice part is, if you fetched it once,
it will never do this again.
你总是只有组件，所以
You will always just have the components,
so
这将是他们第一次提出要求。
this will be the first time they ask for
it.
所以，我要在这里做两件事。
So, I'm gonna do two things here.
我将继续创建一个小的装载器组件，
I'm gonna go ahead and create like
a small little loader component,
这真的很好。
which really good.
这就像是故意取样，应该比我的更好。
It's gonna be like intentionally sample
like, there's should be better than mine.
有没有人想让我调整CSS，因为我很不擅长。
Does anyone wanna me tweak with CSS,
cuz I'm very bad at it.
我们会做一个新的组件，然后
We'll make a new component, and
我们称之为装载。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：和
we'll call it loading.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
在实际的应用程序中，您可能有多个加载器。
in a real application,
you might have multiple loaders.
你可能有一个通用的东西是通用的，
You might have a generic one for
things that are generic,
如果您加载的是整个页面。
if it's an entire page
that you're loading.
但你可能会喜欢，因为
But you might have like, for
一个给定的较小的部分，比如一个更合适的部分。
a given smaller piece,
like one that's more appropriate.
我们的不会那么复杂。
Ours is not gonna be that sophisticated.
我们只是简单地导入，
We'll just simply import,
从反应到反应。
react from react.
我们就像世界上最简单的装载
And we'll just make like
the world's simplest loading
组件。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：它将是一个段落，
component.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: It'll be a paragraph,
它会说正在加载。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：再一次，
and it will say loading.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Again,
就像你的一样，可以说应该更复杂，但是
like yours arguably should
be more sophisticated, but
这不是这件作品的高价值。
that is not the high value of this piece.
好的，整齐。
All right, neat.
现在，让我们拿一些花了我们一些时间的东西。
Now, lets take something
that has taken us some time.
我的想法就像是一面代码镜子。
I think like code mirror.
我们不是反代码镜，我们只是喜欢，不是现在，
We’re not anti code mirror,
we are just like, not now,
我正在尝试加载网页代码镜像，请。
I am trying to load a web
page code mirror, please.
您很大，并且占用了大量的解析时间。
You are large and
you’re taking up a lot of parsing time.
我不需要你。
I don’t need you.
所以我们继续吧。
So lets go ahead.
我的应用程序的结构方式是redux容器模式。
The way my application is structured,
I have the redux container pattern.
所以如果你看一下编辑器，它从我的商店里抓取了一大堆东西
So if you look at the editor, it grabs
a bunch of stuff from my store and
然后传给编辑，对吗？
then passes it to the editor, right?
我很乐意将它传递给编辑器的可加载版本，例如，
I would love to pass it to a loadable
version of the editor like,
在这里，将此数据传递给组件。
here, pass this data to a component.
我一会儿就去拿那些东西。
I'm gonna go fetch that
stuff in a little bit.
所以我要做的是，我要在这里再做一个组件。
So what I'm gonna do,
I'm gonna make one more component here.
我会叫它，可加载编辑器，这将是我的岔路口。
And I'm gonna call it, Loadable Editor and
this is gonna be my fork in the road.
如果已经加载了编辑器组件，请使用它。
If you have the editor component
loaded already, use it.
如果你没有，去拿它，并在同时显示我的加载组件。
If you don't, go get it and show my
loading component in the mean time.
一旦您有了它，请将我切换到编辑器组件。
And once you have it,
switch me over to the editor component.
这说得通吗？
Does that make sense?
很酷，所以让我们继续并快速地编写这个代码。
Cool, so let's go ahead and
code this one up real quick.
所以我们会说，进口反应从‘反应’；。
So we'll say, import React from 'react';.
从‘react-loadable’导入可加载的。
Import Loadable from 'react-loadable'.
我们会说，&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：LoadableEditor和
And we'll say,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: LoadableEditor and
然后我们采用接受对象的可加载方法。
then we take the loadable
method that takes an object.
那需要
That takes
您想要加载的组件，然后在此期间显示什么。
the component that you want to load and
then what to show in the meantime.
所以我们会说，装载者，&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：和
So we'll say, loader,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
我们只要进口我们需要的。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：和
we'll just import the one that we need.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
这是用来处理反应成分的。
this is for
dealing with reaction components.
如果您使用import语句，它将返回一个承诺，然后获取它。
If you use that import statement, it's
gonna return a promise and fetch it then.
你可以将它用于任何类型的代码，
You can use it for any kind of code,
不管它是不是反应成分。
it doesn't matter if it's
a reaction component.
您可以将它用于可能有很多依赖关系的任何事情。
You can use it for anything that
might have a lot of dependencies.
当你会说，去拿这个东西，然后我们就会上前。
When you'll be like, go get this thing,
and then we'll come forward.
所以我们将导入编辑器。
So we'll import the editor.
我们会说加载组件是，
And we'll say that
the loading component is,
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：我会的
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: I will
导出可加载编辑器。
export the loadable editor.
所以现在，我们有了这个新的组件。
So now, we have this new component.
它有智慧去得到它需要的东西。
It has the smarts to get what it needs.
同时显示装载情况。
Show the loading in the meantime.
我们只需要使用它。
We just need to use it.
所以我们接下来要做的就是进入这个编辑器容器，
So what we'll go ahead and
do is we'll go into this editor container,
我们只是要把它换掉。
and we're just gonna swap it out.
我们会说，&gt；&gt；steve kinney：然后
We'll say,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
这实际上不起作用，但我要改名只是为了
this actually doesn't work, but
I'm gonna change the name just to make
一分。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：和
a point.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
我们将在React或Redux容器中使用LoadableEditor。
we'll use the LoadableEditor instead
in our React or Redux container.
好的，我们做到了。
All right, so we did it.
让我们，&gt；&gt；steve kinney：去吧
Let's,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Go ahead and
我必须改变一个设置。
I have to change one setting.
我故意遗漏了这一点，所以你可以看着我做。
I purposely left this out,
so you can watch me do it.
你现在可以看到应用程序崩溃了。
And you can see right
now the app is crashing.
就像，我不明白这个导入语法是什么。
It's like, I don't understand
what this import syntax is.
因此，JavaScript中的新功能在TC39组中经历了一个阶段，
So, new features in JavaScript,
go through a phase in the group TC39,
技术委员会39.
Technical Committee 39.
你可能会问1到38在哪里。
You might ask where are 1 through 38.
我不知道。
I have no idea.
他们是做什么的？
And what do they do?
我不知道。
I don't know.
这都是
This is all part of
正式名称为欧洲计算机制造商协会。
what was formally called the European
Computer Manufacturers Association.
现在刚叫它为什么JavaScript的真名是。
Now just called its why
the real name of JavaScript is.
所以加载，这个导入语法，就是我们所说的第三阶段。
So the loading, this import syntax,
is what we call stage three.
第三阶段意味着语言上没有完全批准，但是
Stage three means not totally
ratified in the language, but
就像是该语言下一个版本的强大候选者。
like pretty much a strong candidate for
the next version of the language.
您将看到Webpack和Babble支持功能
You will see things like,
Webpack and babble support features
几乎很早就完成了，这是可扩展网络宣言的一部分。
that are almost done early, and this is
part of like the extensible web manifesto.
比如，让我们在把这些东西放到开发人员手中之前，尽早把它们拿到手
Of like, let's get these things into
developers hands early before we put them
在语言上。
in the language.
因为如果我们犯了错误或者不去想它
Cuz if we made mistakes or
didn't think about it'd
在语言批准之前获得反馈是很酷的，并且
be cool to get that feedback before
they are ratified in language, and
每个浏览器都必须遵循它们的所有规范。
every browser has to follow
all the spec for them.
所以导入，你需要一个巴别塔插件。
So import,
you do need a babel plugin for this.
如果我们查看JSON包，我们可以看到我已经
If we look in the package JSON,
we can see that I've
得到了这个语法-dynamic-import，这就是我们想要的。
got this syntax-dynamic-import,
which is what we want.
所以继续吧，我们会把它添加到我们的Babel-RC中，
So go ahead and
we'll add that to our babel-rc,
也是。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：和
as well.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
我要杀了之前的服务器。
I'm gonna kill that previous server.
它说编译成功了，但我不相信。
It said compiled it successfully,
but I don't believe it.
很可能是，但是，&gt；&gt；steve kinney：那么
It probably did, but,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Then
我们将刷新页面，&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：和
we'll refresh the page,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
东西会碎的。&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：转型
things will break.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Transform
是自动功能。&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：让我们继续
is autofunction.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Let's go ahead and
去掉自定义loadash代码
get rid of that custom loadash code from
之前。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：是的，
before.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Yeah,
我还有Loadash/Transform
I still had loadash/transform.
就像，一个或另一个，我确实喜欢这里的常规装载器，而且
It's like, one or the other,
I do like regular loadash here, and
插件可以工作。
the plug in will work.
但我在那里寻找变形
But I was looking for
the transform from there and
试图找到它。&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：所以
trying to find its.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So
我们已经变形了。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：和
we've got transform.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
你看我的应用程序在这里。
you see my app is here.
好的，所以这个应用程序在功能上的表现和以前一样。
All right, so the app functionally
behaves the way it did before.
如果你仔细观察，你可以看到那里的小负载。
If you watch for it, you can see
that tiny little loading there.
我给你重放一遍。
I'll replay it for you.
不，那是行不通的。
Nope, that's not gonna work.
从这里重播。
Replay it from here.
要做的事情，仔细观察。
Things to do, watch closely.
我要按编辑按钮，准备好了吗？
I'm gonna hit the Edit button, you ready?
你刚才看到了一堆东西。
You saw a load for a second there.
它最初没有那个代码，它去拿了它，对吧。
It didn't have that code originally,
and it went and got it, right.
如果我有稍微好一点的话，
If I had it slightly nicer,
我可以展示一些看起来几乎像编辑的东西。
I could show something that
almost looked like the editor.
我可以在那里耍一大堆花招，
I could do a whole bunch
of trickery there,
让用户觉得它更快了一点。
to make the user feel like
it's a little snappier.
而且它不在最初的捆绑中，我们去拿了它。
And it wasn't in the initial bundle,
we went and got it.
我们再做一件事。
Let's do one other thing.
我们会重新开始的。&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：我要走了
We'll start over again.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: I'm going
去网络。
to go to the network.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：我将点击编辑，然后
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: I'll hit edit, and
你可以看到，当我们点击编辑器时，我们又得到了两个条目，
you can see that, when we hit the editor,
we got two more entries,
网络选项卡中的两个小条目，对。
two small entries in the network tab,
right.
因为那时我去找了那个编辑。
Cuz that's when I went and
got that editor.
现在，我想向大家展示的是，这个包分析器看起来像什么。
Now, what I want to show you is, what
this looks like with the bundle analyzer.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：嗯，C就像一个大的
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Well C is like a large
我们，我们有一个捆绑的方式不同，我们把低破折号减少了百分之十。
difference in the way that our, we had
one bundle, we cut down low dash by 10%.
很好，对吧？
That was good, right?
我们对此感觉很好。
We're feeling pretty good about that.
我认为当我们看到下一段代码时会非常有趣。
I think it will really interesting
when we see the next piece of code.
运行可视化行为，
Run acts of visualization,
也就是说，你可以看到，我们现在生产了两个捆绑包，实际上是三个捆绑包。
which is you can see that we're now
producing two bundles, actually three.
这是我们的主要，这是我们最初的应用，现在下降到272，对。
Which is our main, which is our initial
application, is now down to 272, right.
从450。所以现在我们低于300的门槛。
From 450.
So now we're under that 300 threshold.
对，因为我们有代码镜子和你需要的一切。
Right, cuz we have code mirror and
everything you need.
你能去那边吗？
Can you go over there?
我们待会再找你。
We'll get you later.
所以我们得到了初始渲染时间，这些关键资产，所以
So we get that initial render time,
those critical assets, so
用户看到我们的页面。
the user sees our page.
还记得我们一开始谈到的所有统计数据吗？
Remember all those statistics that
we talked about in the beginning?
如果页面需要加载的内容多于要加载的内容，并且
If the page takes more
than whatever to load, and
加载包括解析，正如我们所讨论的。
load includes parsing, as we discussed.
花了这么多时间，然后他们就走了。
It takes all this time to do it,
then they leave.
我们已经说过了，嘿，让我们把你留下来的第一页给你，
We've said, hey, let's get you
the initial page that you stay,
我们稍后会给你剩下的。
and we'll get you the rest later.
所以我们的捆绑现在降到了272。
So our bundle is now down to 272.
整个182，因为有一些组件和
A whole 182,
cuz there was some components and
里面的其他东西也在进行中。
other stuff in there that's
going along as well.
我们会去那里，在那个包裹里。
We'll go there, in that bundle.
我们还会有另一个很小的，里面没有多少东西。
Also we'll have this other tiny one,
which has got not much in it.
我们可以看到它太小了。
We can see it's too small.
我们可以看到，我们已经分出了最大的问题在那里。
We can see that we have already split
out the biggest problem in there.
但我们还可以做更多的事。
But there's more that we can do.
我不知道这是哪个人物实体。
I don't know which
character entity is this.
但我确实知道这个注释解析是什么，它是mark down组件，对吧？
But I do know what this remark parse is,
it's the mark down component, right?
同样，当他们第一次看到初始登录页面时，
And again, when they first see
that initial landing page,
我们不会用那个。
we're not using that.
在他们真正去查看笔记之前，我们不会使用它。
We're not using that until they
actually go to view a note.
那我们现在为什么要发货呢？
So why are we shipping it now?
为什么我们要花钱把它塞进猫的管子里？
Why are we paying the cost of
shoving it through the tube of cats?
为什么我们现在要解析它，而我们可以稍后再做，而不是现在呢？
Why are we parsing it right now,
when we can do it later and not do it now?
那么，让我们看看我对编辑做了什么。
So, let's look at what
I did with the editor.
我做了一个加载组件，它是可重用的，因为它很傻。
I made a loading component,
which is reusable because it's silly.
我做了，我用React Loadable制作了一个组件，基本上
I made, I used react loadable to
make a component that's basically
道路上的岔路口。
a fork in the road.
去拿吧，如果你没有的话。
Go get it, if you don't have it.
同时显示这个正在加载的一个。
Show this loading one in the meantime.
需要注意的重要一点是，它只会获取一次。
The important thing to note is
that it will only fetch that once.
如果我看其他笔记，它已经有编辑器了。
If I watch other notes,
it already has the editor.
它不会再去拿了，这太酷了。
It's not gonna go get it again,
which is super cool.
然后在我的编辑器里
And then in my editor here,
我刚刚换掉了这里的编辑器，换成了可加载的编辑器。
I just swapped out the editor here,
for the loadable editor.